where are you going?
どこに行くの?
While we were chatting on line, I asked Hikari about her favorite places.
ラインでやり取りしてる時に、ひかりが好きな場所聞いちゃってる
From.
から さ
Oh, I see, I said it.
あ、そっかそっか、言ったわ
Do you remember that story?
あの話、覚えてる?
I remember, I remember.
覚えてる、覚えてる
Well then, it's fine.
じゃあ、せーのでいいよ
Seino, Aquarium!
せーの、水族館!
Perfect!
ピッタリー!
Because I knew that I absolutely loved it.
絶対好きって、分かってたから
Wow, did you find out?
わー、バレてたか
It's been about 2 weeks since I lined up, so I haven't done it yet.
ラインして2週間くらいじゃん、まだ
Yes, that's right.
そうか、そうだね
From now on, it feels like the two of us have finally met.
これからしたら、ようやく2人で会えたって感じだね
Well, before, we were never alone together.
まあね、前はね、2人っきりってなかったもんね
I've never had anyone around me before.
今まで周りに誰かしらいたじゃん
Yes, it was.
うん、いたいた
I'm seriously nervous today.
マジで緊張するわ、今日
Me too.
私もだよね
It's getting a little hot.
ちょっと暑くなってきたわ
Oh, seriously?
あ、マジ?
Shall I keep your jacket?
上着預かろうか
good?
いい?
Okay.
いいよ
Please, come on.
お願いするわ、じゃあ
Wow, that dress is cute.
わ、可愛い、その服
real?
ほんと?
Yeah, it's so cute.
うん、めちゃめちゃ可愛い
Well, it's thin after all.
てか、やっぱ、細い
Stop it, really.
やめてよ、ほんとに
It's insanely thin.
めちゃめちゃ細い
Good style.
スタイルいい
It's super stylish.
超スタイルいいじゃん
Stop praising me like this.
こんな褒めないで、やめて
I'm shy.
恥ずかしがりや
I think it's probably the entrance.
入り口、多分そっちの方だと思うんだよね
Is it this way?
こっちかな?
Yeah.
うん
Let's go.
行ってみよう
Yeah, let's go.
うん、行ってみよう
Shall we go?
行ってみよう?
Yay.
イエーイ
Wow, what is this fish?
わー、なにこの魚
Look at this.
これ見てみな
Amazing, amazing.
すごい、すごい
What is this?
なに、これ?
Wow, that's super cute.
わー、超かわいい
What kind of fish is this?
これなんていう魚だろう?
Well, I wonder what you'll say.
ね、なんて言うんだろう
It looks delicious though.
美味しそうなのに
picture?
え?
By any chance, are you hungry?
まさか、お腹減ってんの?
looks delicious.
美味しそう
Looks like it's edible.
食べれそうだよ
It looks like a face.
顔みたいな顔してる
picture?
え?
You're comparing everything to food.
全部食べ物に例えてるじゃん
No.
違うよ
I'm not that gluttonous.
そんな食いしん坊じゃないもん
real?
ほんと?
That's not true.
そんなことないよ
I like eating a lot.
結構食べるの好き
Look, isn't that cute too?
見て、あれもかわいくない?
So cute.
めっちゃかわいい
You're full of energy.
元 気いっぱいだね
Are you full of energy?
元気いっぱい?
Full of energy.
元気いっぱい
Look.
見て
Wow, that's amazing.
わー、すごい
amazing.
すごい
Amazing, fast.
すごい、速い
It's insanely fast.
めちゃめちゃ速い
So cute.
めっちゃかわいい
Huh?
あれ?
Oh no.
やべえ
picture?
え?
What is this?
なにこれ?
Hikare-chan's face is turning red.
ひかれちゃん、顔赤くなってる
In the light above.
上の光で
But, this feeling is also really cute.
でもね、この感じもすごいかわいい
it was good.
良かった
I'm drawn in when I look at that face.
なんか引き込まれちゃうな、その顔見てると
picture?
え?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいよ
Stop it.
やめてよ
No?
ダメ?
Shall I say it?
言っちゃう?
Things like this.
こういうこと
Okay though.
いいけど
Okay then.
じゃあいいじゃん
good?
いい?
Okay.
いいよ
Come on.
おいで
go.
行く
I'm eating.
食べてる
Wow, that's cute.
わー、かわいい
It's so cute.
めちゃめちゃかわいい
delicious?
おいしい?
What did you say?
なんて言ってた?
He said it was delicious.
美味しいって言ってたよ
Do you want it?
いりますか?
Ah, I ate it.
あ、食べた
I ate it.
食べたよ
I want to eat it too.
俺も食べたいな
It's like a battle of purity versus purity.
純粋対純粋の戦いって感じ
What do you mean?
何のこと?
The aquarium and cat cafe were both really fun.
水族館も猫カフェもめっちゃ楽しかったね
It was really fun.
すごい楽しかった
If you like something, I'll buy it for you.
何かよければ買ってあげる?
souvenir.
お土産
It's beautiful.
キレイだね
For two people.
2人で
What would you like?
何がいいかな?
What is that?
あれは?
copper?
どう?
Isn't it interesting?
面白くない?
Look, look.
見て見て
interesting.
面白い
T-shirt.
Tシャツ
This is a T-shirt, right?
これTシャツだよね?
T-shirts, T-shirts.
Tシャツ、Tシャツ
Let's make the two of us match.
2人でお揃いにしようよ
nice.
いいね
It's really good.
めっちゃいいじゃん
I want you to wear this pink one.
こっちのピンクのやつを着て欲しいから
OK, make it pink.
OK、ピンクにする
Hikaru-chan is pink.
ヒカルちゃんピンクね
So I guess I'll just pop in.
じゃあ俺はポッチンしようかな
nice.
いいね
Feels good.
いい感じ
This is perfect for two people.
これ2人でお揃い
Let's do that.
そうしよう
OK
Shall I buy it then?
じゃあ買ってくる?
Yeah, thank you.
うん、ありがとう
It got dark before I knew it.
いつの間にか暗くなっちゃったね
It all happened so quickly.
なんかあっという間に
I found a nice place.
いい場所見つけたんだけど
Come with me.
一緒に来て
Okay.
いいよ
There are people around there right now, but you can't see them from here.
今その辺に人とかいるけど、 ここだったらちょっと見えないから
I think it's okay.
大丈夫 だと思うんだよね
Really?
本当に?
I really mean it.
本当に言ってる
good?
いい?
Yeah, okay.
うん、いいよ
They put it out because it's this good.
こんなにいいから出してたんだね
That's not true.
そんなことないよ
Seriously, I said that a lot.
マジでよくそう言いちゃったわ
And it looks incredibly easy to lick.
しかもすごいなめやすそう
What are you talking about?
何言ってるの?
terrible.
やばい
Your underwear is so cute.
下着めっちゃかわいいね
You'll find out.
バレちゃうよ
it's okay.
大丈夫だよ
I'm sad.
悲しんでいるよ
Yeah, brain pants.
うん、脳パンツね
I took off my brain pants.
脳パンツを脱いだ
brain pants
脳 パ ンツ を
I took it off.
脱 いだ
I'm wearing brain pants now.
今脳パンツだよ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
difficult.
難しい
difficult?
難しい?
But I also want to see that embarrassing side.
でもその恥ずかしい姿も見たいんだよね
It's so erotic, isn't it?
めっちゃエロいでしょ
A naughty sill is showing.
エッチなシル出てる
Hyo-san, just leave it like this, let's watch some more together, just the two of us.
ひょうさん、このままさ、2人だけでもっと一緒に見ようよ
Take a closer look in a brighter area.
もっと明るいところでよく見して
So, shall we go somewhere where we can be alone?
じゃあ2人っきりになるとこ行く?
Hello, staff.
こんにちは、スタッフ
Your hair is smooth.
さらさらだね、髪の毛
soft.
柔らかい
It's super soft.
めっちゃ柔らかい
It's cold, isn't it?
冷たいよね
Yeah, nice.
うん、いいね
Can you feel my breasts?
おっぱい感じる?
cormorant
う
yeah.
ん
Are you touching my breasts or my inner neck?
お っぱいさ、内首触ってる?
difficult.
難しい
So, I turned into an M shape and looked at the panties with my feet.
そこでさ、M字になって足でパンツ見して
picture?
え?
beautiful.
きれい
Open your legs and show me.
足開いて見せて
A cute one came in.
かわいいの入ってきちゃって
Hey, it's cute.
ね、かわいい
There's hair here.
毛があるよ、ここに
I don't like it.
嫌だね
Where is it here?
ど こ に ある の、ここ?
sometimes.
時々
I don't know yet.
まだわからない
I'll paint my panties.
パンティー塗るから
I wonder if this fits.
合ってるかな、これ
Does it match?
合ってる?
It's difficult, isn't it?
難しいよね
difficult.
難しい
Take a look at this difficult part.
その難しいところで、ここ見して
Don't touch it.
触らない
Are you wet now?
今濡れてる?
moisten
濡
It's been done.
れて る
Are you wet?
濡れてんの?
Lift your butt a little.
ちょっとお尻浮かして
I'm so wet.
めっちゃ濡れてる
Liquid is stuck to my pants.
パンツに液がこびりついてる
Don't look.
見ないで
Are you watching?
見てる?
pants.
パンツ
It's wet.
濡れてるよ
It's so wet.
すごい濡れてる
Check this out for yourself.
自分で確認してみて、これ
Ah, I'm out of breath.
ああ、息が垂れちゃう
Your skirt will get wet.
スカートに濡れちゃうね
this.
これ
A lot of juice is dripping into this.
めっちゃ汁この中に垂れてる
I want to see inside this.
この中見たい
Shall we see it?
見ちゃう?
I want to see it.
見たい
Can you open it and show me?
開いて見せてくれる?
This way, with both hands.
こっちか、両手で
I know you're sleeping, myself.
寝 てるの分かるよね、自分で
Have you ever slept?
いつか寝てたの?
You've been sleeping since you were at the chair aquarium, right?
椅子族館にいるときから寝てたでしょ?
Maybe.
もしかして
Well, there isn't one.
さて、いないですね
This is a private place.
こっちの民間のところだよね
Everything looks like money.
全部マネ見え
The clitoris.
クリトリスを
I ate a turtle.
カメ食っちゃった
What were you doing just now?
今何してたの?
Say it again.
もう一回言って
What are you doing to your clitoris now?
今クリトリス何してんの?
this.
これ
Say it again.
もう一回言って
What are you rubbing?
何をこすってんの?
So, shall we lick it?
じゃあ、ぺろぺろしちゃう?
Do you like licking?
ぺろぺろがいい?
Which one is better?
どっちがいい?
Licking?
ぺろぺろと?
Do you rub it?
こするの?
Which one is better?
どっちがいい?
sour.
酸っぱい
This makes Skirt Meiryo sour.
これ、スカートメイリオ酸っぱいなって
Wow, so beautiful.
うわ、すごく綺麗
So beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗
The style is really nice.
スタイルめっちゃいいじゃん
cute.
かわいい
amazing.
すごい
Look behind me.
後ろ見えて
Look behind you.
後ろ見して
cute butt.
かわいいお尻
Will you be the fourth one there?
そこで四つ目になってくれる?
nostalgic?
懐かしい?
now.
今
You can see around my butt.
お尻の周り見えだよ
what happened?
どうしたの?
Does it feel good here?
ここ気持ちいい?
cold?
冷たい?
Let's lick it a lot.
いっぱい舐めちゃおう
Does your butt feel good?
お尻も気持ちいい?
It feels really good.
すっごい気持ちよさそう
It's called a virtual rear ceiling.
仮想後天井ってやつだね
Shall we go?
行っちゃう?
I want to see if I can go.
行くかも見たい
Look here.
こっち見て
This butt is amazing.
尻がすごいよこれ
It keeps dripping.
垂れっぱなしになっちゃってる
My butt is hanging out.
尻が垂れっぱなしになっちゃってる
Since when did you end up in that position?
いつからそんな位置になっちゃったの?
It's starting to hurt a lot.
めっちゃ痛くなってきちゃった
It's so murky.
めっちゃミュルミュル
It felt so good.
めっちゃ気持ちよかった
on second thoughts.
やっぱり
This might feel too good.
これ気持ちよすぎるかも
I don't like my nature.
自 分の性質は嫌だな
Look.
見て
It's the matching one from earlier.
さっきのお揃いのやつだ
Would you like to try it on?
着てみる?
Let's try it on.
着てみよう
What do you think?
どうかな?
Does it suit you?
似合うかな?
It looks good on me.
似合うそうだよ
I'm writing on TV 24 hours a day.
24時間テレビで書いてる
surely.
確かに
Talk about humans.
人間話しね
Is it okay because the punishment is light?
仕首薄けてるからいい?
It's embarrassing, this is a sketcher.
恥ずかしいね、これスケッチャー
That's really good.
めっちゃいいじゃん、それ
Does it feel good?
いい感じ?
It's definitely dangerous.
しっかりやばしい
I'm so embarrassed.
すごく恥ずかしい
shame
恥ず
Strange appearance.
か しい姿
I took off a lot of clothes, again.
いっぱい脱いできちゃった、また
Do you like this?
こういうの好き?
Have you ever used it?
使ったことあるの?
first time?
初めて?
good?
いい?
Put on your clothes and make them boobs.
服を着ておっぱいにして
Wow, that's it.
うわ、いっちー
What's going to happen?
何が起きそう?
Are you about to wake up?
起きそう?
Well then, take this picture of your own face.
じゃあ、これ自分で自分の顔を撮ってって
Itchi.
いっちー
I'll tell you exactly when I go.
行くときちゃんと言うんだよ
cute?
かわいい?
No more?
もうダメ?
What will happen?
どうなるの?
What happens if I continue?
つづけたらどうなるの?
What will happen?
どうなるの?
Doesn't it feel good?
気持ちいいんじゃないの?
I did this, so what?
こう やったから、何?
Is it okay to guess?
当てちゃダメなの?
But I want to guess.
でも当てたくなっちゃう
It's the sun again.
また太陽だね
I told him that I had a naughty smell coming from the sun.
それに向かって、私太陽にエッチな臭い出ちゃったって報告して
I won't be able to put my hands in my pussy anymore,
マンコンに手色たんびり入れなくなっちゃう、
This mancon.
このマンコン
It feels so good I'll definitely do this again.
気持ちいい絶対これまた
I get sucked into it.
吸い込まれちゃう
But I think that's how it will grow.
でも、そうやって大きくなってくると思う
do?
する?
feeling
気持
Good.
ち いい
Wow, it feels good.
うわ、気持ちいい
Oh my gosh, this pussy is amazing.
やばい、このマンコンってね
The naughty smell is sticky.
エッチな臭いが粘ついてる
Can you sneak it in on this side?
こっち側で忍ばせられる?
Try taking the dick yourself.
自 分でチンコを持っていってみて
Would you like to see this?
これ見ちゃう?
It feels amazing.
すごい気持ちいい
My dick is sitting.
チンコ座ってる